Guide to the Kate Bornstein papers 1910-2018
Brown University Library
- Conferences, 1991-2017
  - 2010 - IDKE XII: Gender Justice conference (Baltimore, Maryland); contains program (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 2011 - Post Posttranssexual: Transgender Studies and Feminism Conference (Indiana University); contains progam and letter from organizers (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 2013 - Women and Society Conference (Marist College); includes Ms. Magazine featuring reproductive rights activist, Wendy Davis (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 2014 - National Undergraduate Conference on Body Image (Cabrini College); contains packet material (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 2015 - 7th Annual LGBTQI Health Forum (University of California, San Francisco); contains information sheets and bio information re: Bornstein (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 2015 - CatalystCon East re: human sexuality; contains booklet (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 2015 - Transgender Film Festival (New York University); contains program (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 2016 - Queer Contact and Sex Humanities Festival (Manchester, United Kingdom and Manchester Metropolitan University); contain programs (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 2017 - Identity (Casper College Humanities Festival); contains program (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 2017 - National Playwrght's Conference (Eugene O'Neill Theater Center); contains information sheets, program and voided checks to Bornstein (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - N.D. - Trans - Ally Beginner Workshop (Susquehanna University); contains information sheets (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Writings by Kate Bornstein, 1970-2013
  - AMFAR Gender Defender Infomercial (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Anna: monologue re: Bornstein coming out to mother as trans as told from mother's perspective. From Virtually Yours solo performance., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Another American Legacy re: Condoleeza Rice: essay (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - The Art of Prayer: essay draft, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Artist's Statement, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Best of Best Lesbian Erotica: royalty check; contains check re: Bornstein's article contribution, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Beyond Red or Blue re: United States presidential election: essay draft, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Blonde Trans-thing Does Sex, Death and Gender: essay draft, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Caress: section draft re: unidentified title (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Chapter 3: How Candy Became a Member of the Galactic Librartion Alliance, and In What Manner It Was Discovered That Her Heart Was Pure: essay draft (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Cut 'N' Paste: play version 2.1.5 by Kate Bornstein and Barbara Carrellas, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Cut 'N' Paste: play version 2.2 by Kate Bornstein and Barbara Carrellas, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Cut 'N' Paste: play version 2.3 by Kate Bornstein and Barbara Carrellas, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Cut 'N' Paste: play version [?] by Kate Bornstein and Barbara Carrellas, 1999, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Cut 'N' Paste: publicity, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Dangerous Dreams, Damned Desires: essay drafts. See also talks, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Dixie Belle: The Further Adventures of Huckleberry Finn: essay, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - From a Gender Outlaw on Men, Women, and the Rest of Us: book draft, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Gender Outlaw: permissions agreements and publicity, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - G.I.D.G.E.T., Beta 2.0 (booklet), 2005 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - The Gyrl With No Name: script, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Hard Candy: The Tragic Lives and Comical Deaths of Candy Bromowitz (partial draft/notes of fictionalized autobiography) (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Hello, Cruel Bullies: essay, ca.2005 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Hello, Cruel Bullies: essay draft, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Hello, Cruel Desire: essay draft, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Hello, Cruel Desire: essay draft, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Hello, Cruel Desire: essay draft, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Hello, Cruel Desire: essay draft, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Hello, Cruel Desire: essay (final); includes booklet, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Hello, Cruel Desire for College: essay draft, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - The Hello Cruel Quick-Start Guide: essay draft, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Hello, Cruel World: book covers, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Hello, Cruel World: book draft; includes correspondence, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Hello, Cruel World: book draft; includes correspondence, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Hello, Cruel World: book draft, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Hello, Cruel World: book draft, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Hello, Cruel World: book draft, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Hello, Cruel World: book draft, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Hello, Cruel World: book draft, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Hello, Cruel World: book draft, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Hello, Cruel World: draft pages and notes (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Hello, Cruel World: draft section, "101 Alternatives to Teen Suicide", 2004, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hello, Cruel World: draft section, "Hello, Cruel Bullies;" includes correspondence, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Hello, Cruel World: draft section, "Hello, Cruel Desire", n.d. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Hello, Cruel World: image rights photocopies, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Hello, Cruel World: publishing correspondance and interview talking points re: suicide, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hello, Cruel World Lite: booklet drafts, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Her Son/Daugher: offprint article from New York Times Magazine. See also "Hoowayoo?" (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Hidden: A Gender: copyright registration, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Hidden: A Gender: play, first draft, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Hidden: A Gender: play, second draft, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Hidden: A Gender: play, third draft, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Hidden: A Gender: programs and publicity, 1989, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Hoowahyoo?: essay draft. See Also "Her Son/Daughter", 1998, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Kate Bornstein is a Queer and Pleasant Danger: A Solo Performance: script, first draft, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Kate Bornstein is a Queer and Pleasant Danger: A Solo Performance: script, first draft revision, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Kate Bornstein is a Queer and Pleasant Danger: A Solo Performance: script, performance version 1, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Kate Bornstein is a Queer and Pleasant Danger: A Solo Performance: script, performance version 1.5, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Kate Bornstein is a Queer and Pleasant Danger: A Solo Performance: script, rehersal version, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Kate Bornstein is a Queer and Pleasant Danger: A Solo Performance: script, scene I draft, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Kate Bornstein is a Queer and Pleasant Danger: A Solo Performance: script, scene II drafts, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Kate Bornstein is a Queer and Pleasant Danger: A Solo Performance: script, scene V draft, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Kate Bornstein is a Queer and Pleasant Danger: A Solo Performance: script, technical script; includes CD-R video, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Kate Bornstein is Y2K Gender Virus 2000: script, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Kate To Boy (script), n.d. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - LGBT Quit-smoking Video: script, first draft and outline, ca.1999 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - The Little Macho Girl: essay, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Lunar Rocks: Some Thoughts on "Romancing A Stone [art exhibit by Karin Lunar]" (1 of 2), 2000 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Lunar Rocks: Some Thoughts on "Romancing A Stone [art exhibit by Karin Lunar];" contains orignial sketches by Karin Lunar (2 of 2), 2000 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Message In A Bottle: essay, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Minus and Music: essay (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Mr. Blunt: essay (paragraph), n.d. (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - My Father's Dream: essay (partial), n.d. (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - My Gender Workbook: book draft, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - My Gender Workbook: book draft (partial) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - My Gender Workbook: edited pages from"Rhinestones: 57 Varieties", ca.1996 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - My Gender Workbook: editorial queries, ca.2013 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - My Gender Workbook: exceprt booklet, ca.1996 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - My Gender Workbook: permissions, 1997, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - My Gender Workbook: press, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - My Gender Workbook: press kits, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - My Gender Workbook: publishing contract, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - My Name Is… And This Is My Gender Workbook: book draft (1 of 2), ca.1995 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - My Name Is… And This Is My Gender Workbook: book draft (1 of 2), ca.1995 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Nearly RoadKill: book draft by Kate Bornstein and Cailtlin Sullivan (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Nearly RoadKill: book draft by Kate Bornstein and Cailtlin Sullivan (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Nearly Roadkill: chapters 1 and 5 partial drafts (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Nearly Roadkill: press, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Nearly Roadkill: publishing contract and correspondence, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - A One-Sided Conversation: essay draft, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - One With No Name: sript draft, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - The Opposite Sex… Is Neither: scripts, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - The Opposite Sex… Is Neither: scripts, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - The Opposite Sex… Is Neither: scripts, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - The Opposite Sex… Is Neither: technical scripts, ca.1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - The Opposite Sex… Is Neither: technical scripts, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Post Hard: A Cyberplay In One Act and Many Windows: script, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 1 draft (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 1 draft (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 1 draft (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 2 draft (partial) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 2.1 draft (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 2.2 draft (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 2.3 draft (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 2.3 draft (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 2.4 draft (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 2.4 draft, "Pateints" (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 2.5 draft (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 2.6 draft (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 2.6 draft, "Man Without a Family (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 3.1 draft (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 3.1 draft (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 3.2 draft (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 3.4 draft (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 3.5, "Everybody Else's Girl" (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book 3.5, "Girl" (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: book draft (bound) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: "Chapter One: Dark Roots of a Killer Blonde" draft (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: "Chapter Four: All At Sea" draft (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: "Chapter Four: Bone White, Blood Red" draft (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: draft section re: scientology (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: "Love Was Never Free" draft re: scientology (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: "Mildred in Belmar" draft (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: outlines (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: "Preface: Letter From the Earth" draft (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: page proofs, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: promotional material, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: publishing agreements and royalties, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger: unidentified draft sections (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Seascapes; contains poem published in Loomings: The Penningtn School Literary Journal, Volume 1, Number 1, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Segue Seven Year Itch and Mr. Blunt: draft essay (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - The Seven Year Itch: What Goes Around, Comes Around: script, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Sex, Bullies and You: How Amercian Bully Culture Is Messing With Your Sex Life: essay (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Sex, Truth, and Performance Art: My Kind of Candidate: essay (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Sexy: essay drafts, 1999, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, "first workshop script", 1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, "first workshop script copies, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, "first workshop script copies, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, partial script #1, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, partial script #2, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, technical script, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, version 3.0, ca.2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, version 4.3, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, version 4.5, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, version 4.75, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, version 5.0, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, version 6.0, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, version 6.2, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, version 6.5, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Strangers in Paradox: script, version 8.1.1, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Strangers in Paradox: press, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Strangers in Paradox: production agreement, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Too Tall Blondes Do Sex, Death, and Gender: script drafts, ca.1999 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Too Tall Blondes Do Sex, Death, and Gender: scripts, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Too Tall Blondes In Love: script draft, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Too Tall Blondes In Love: script draft, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Too Tall Blondes In Love: script draft, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Too Tall Blondes In Love: script; includes CD-R labeled "TTBIL Sound", 2001 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Too Tall Blondes In Love and Art Amongst the Ruins: script draft, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Trans: Shifting Sands, Quicksand or Ampersand: essay, ca.2015 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Transsexual Lesbian Playwright Tells All: essay, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Unidentified title: essay draft re: paradoxes, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Unidentified title: play, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Unidentified title: script, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified title: script, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified titles, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Until When?: short essay re: death, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Untitled: "personal writings", 1984, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Various titles: poems, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Various titles: talks, 1987-1997 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Various titles: talks, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Various titles: talks, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Various titles: talks, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Various titles: talks; includes "American Bully Culture and How It Messes with Your Sex Life", 2005 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Various titles: talks, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Various titles: talks, 2008-2010 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Various titles: talks; includes three versions of "Dangerous Dreams/Damned Desires, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Various titles: talks, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Various titles: talks, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Virtually Yours: A Game for Solo Performers with Audience: scripts, version 1.0, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Virtually Yours: A Game for Solo Performers with Audience: scripts, version alpha 4.0, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Virtually Yours: A Game for Solo Performers with Audience: scripts, version beta 1.0, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Virtually Yours: A Game for Solo Performers with Audience: technical scripts, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - The Voice Lesson: essay, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - What I Know About Dick That I Didn't Know Before They Cut Mine Off: essay, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Where's the Sex?: essay draft, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - You Say You Want a Revolution: script, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Wrintings by other authors (unpublished), 1986-2014
  - Abbott, Franklin: untitled poem, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Alford, Becky: Trans Trouble: Kate Bornstein and the Subversion of Identity (paper) (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Beata, Virginia: Damaged Goods (play), n.d. (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Baker, Victoria Goodwin: Fem/Butch (essay), n.d. (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Beatty, Christine: People Like You and Me (essay), 1993 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Bergman, Sharon Jill Bear: Butch Is a Noun (manuscript); includes note by Bornstein, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Bergman, Sharon Jill Bear: Questions Not To Be Asked (manuscript), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Bergstedt, Spenser: Translegalities: A Legal Guide for FTM's and MTF's (guides) [2 volumes], 1997 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Blumrosen, Dana R.: Fantasies of Gender in Comics (manuscript), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Borkhuis, Charles: Barely Three (play), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Borkhuis, Charles: Escape Velocity (play), 2006 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Boyd, Helen: She's Not The Man I Married: My Life with a Transgender Husband (manuscript) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - BrianKate: Battling with Barbie (essay) and Only in America (poem), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Brooks-Livingston, Etan S.: Beyond Intrsectionality: Trans-Situating Difference Through Queer Theory (thesis), 2006 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Carney, Josephine: Purple Hearts and Silver Stars: Poems, Rants, Essays Direct from a Trans-woman's Soul; includes correspondence, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Chayana, Avadim: Once We Were Slaves: A Seder for the Leather Community (script), n.d. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Cohen, Rob: Shape Shifter (poem), n.d. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Cohen, Tamara and Jacob Benmosche Lieberman: Supplement for GenderQueer Trans Inclusive Davenning, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - D., Mrs.: untitled play, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Dibbell, Dominique: The Naked Man Piece (script), 1999 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Donsky, Seth Michael: The Trouble With Safe Sex (article), 2009 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Edwards, Kari: A Day In the Life of P. (manuscript), 2001 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Edwards, Kari: Post/ (Pink) (manuscript), 1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Erickson-Schroth, Laura: Common Histories: Genealogies of Modern Categories of Gender, Sexuality, and Race (thesis), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Erickson-Schroth, Laura: The Making of the Transgender Subject: A Genealogy (paper), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Fierce, Tasha: My Kind of Crazy (manuscript) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Fisher, W.S.: The Succubus: An Artist's Journey Into Saddomasochism (manuscript), 1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Fried, Ian: Rewriting Gender: The Emergence of Transgender Culture Wrtiting (thesis), 1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Fryer, Donna Ross: untitled manuscript, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gates, Katherine: Deviant Desires: Incredibly Strange Sex (manuscript), n.d. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Gottlieb, Daphne (editor): Fucking Daphne (manuscript), n.d. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Grass, Bobby: Do-Another-Gender Day Reflection (paper), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Green, Myla (editor): Women's Narratives of Self-hate", 2005 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Hamilton, Mary Elizabeth: The Quiet Ones (script), 2017 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Hernandez, Michael M.: Transgender MANifesto (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Hurkman, Alexis Van: The Hintrs (play), 2004 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Jones, Uhura: I Was Taught (personal narrative), 2000 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Kaufman, MJ: Eat and You Belong To Us (script) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Kaveney, Roz: Adore and Serve: A Novel of the Fantastic (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Kaveney, Roz: Soft Facts: A Memoir, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Kelly, Mareen: My Body My Rules (manuscript), 1996 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Kilborn, Katie: A Queen, A King, and a Mission re: Bornstein, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Kilborn, Katie: No Longer Underground: TRANSitions In the Liminal Space (undergraduate thesis); includes correspondence, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Kilborn, Katie: Underground Transportation (play proposal) (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Kinginger, Jessica: For Kate (poem), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Leondar-Wright, Betsy and Gail: Killing Time: A Lisa Pillard Mystery (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Mahoney, Mickey Ray: Traverse City (script), 2007 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mantorama [?], Miki: untitled poems, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Miller, Tim: Shirts and Skin (manuscript); includes correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Neem, Sabina: Transitions, Transpositions, Transparents (paper), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Odendahl, Julie Anne: Interogating A Queer Outlaw: Kate Bornstein's Hidden: A Gender: A Director's Approach (thesis), 1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - O'Keefe, Trace and Katrina Fox: Trans People In Love (manuscript); contains partial draft without forward written by Barbara Carellas and Kate Bornstein (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Olson, Alix [editor]: Word Warriors: 35 Women Leaders in the Spoken Word Revolution; includes correspondence to Kate Bornstein, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Oropal, Cheryl Lynne: "Ladies' Room" and "Womyn" (poems), 2006 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Pancake, Ann: Tough (essay) and Virtual Hillbilly (essay) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Park, Pauline: The radically Constructive Turn (paper), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Parker, Wendy Susan: The Berdache Spirit (paper) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Pauling, Monique L. and Alisa S. Beaver: Feminist Approaches to Trangender Psychology (paper), 1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Pianta, Lane: 65 Days (script); includes correspondence, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Portland LOP'ers: Language of Paradox (first draft partial script); contains play directed by Kate Bornstein and produced by Two Gyrls Productions. [Language of Paradox was a week-long workshop for at-risk queer youth in Portland, OR. The script was the final exercise based on the question, "what gives you the most fun and gets you in the most trouble?"], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Portland LOP'ers: Language of Paradox (first draft partial script), 2004 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Portland LOP'ers: Language of Paradox (first draft partial script), 2004 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Portland LOP'ers: Language of Paradox (partial script), 2004 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Portland LOP'ers: Language of Paradox (script), 2004 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Portland SMYRC and Friends: The Show With No Name (scripts and related material); contains play directed by Kate Bornstein and produced by Two Gyrls Productions, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Rose, Katrina C.: A Year (or so) of Kat: A Collection of Comments, Rants, and Other Kat-yowls from the Twilight of the 1990s, ca.1999 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Roth, Brianna: Unforgettable Invisibles (paper), 2005 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Ruhl, Sarah: Orlando (play adapted by Ruhl), 2007 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Samumba [?], A.M.: I Am A Man (poem), n.d. (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Savatdy, Viengmany: Gender: American's Ultimate Hidden Flaw (essay), 2001 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Schulman, Sarah: The Child (script), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Schultz, Mona Lisa: The Intuitive Advisor: A Psychic Doctor Teaches You How to Solve Your Most Pressing Health Problems (manuscript), n.d. (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Serano, Julia: Whipping Girl: A Transsexual Woman on Sexism and the Scapegoating of Feminity (manuscript) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - ShimKovitz, Melissa: Living Pleasantly with Others (play), n.d. (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Smith, Riana: Bodies (poem), n.d. (Box 11, Folder 29)